Guide to the William S. Downing papers, 1922-2006.
Downing, William S. papers,
- Series II. Project Records
  - Spencer School - Kitchen Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 38)
    Project # 215
  - Spencer School - Parapet Repairs Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 38)
    Project # 245
  - School Prospects - Holt, Architect, 1953-1954 (Box 38)
  - C.E. Treman Jr. - Holt, Architect, 1958 (Box 38)
  - Flight - Holt, Architect, 1959 (Box 38)
  - Townley Motors, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1953 (Box 38)
  - Business (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous Estimates, Computations, Data (Box 38)
  - Chenango Valley State Park Septic Tank, 1935 (Box 39)
  - West Hill School - Holt, Architect (Box 39)
  - Ithaca Schools, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 39)
  - Belle Sherman - Preliminary Drawings, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 39)
  - East Hill - Preliminary Drawings, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 39)
  - South Hill - Preliminary Drawings, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 39)
  - Tioga Center Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 39)
  - Reconstruction Home, Ithaca, New York (Box 40)
  - Reconstruction Home, Garage, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 40)
  - First Congregational Church, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1960 (Box 40)
  - First Congregational Church - Drawings, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
  - Junior High School - East Steps Specification - Holt, Architect, 1957 (Box 40)
    Project # 274
  - Junior High School - Temporary Shop Building Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
    Project # 266
  - Junior High and Central School - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
    Project # 246
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi - Specifications, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
    Project # 254
  - Gaskill Residence - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
  - T.N. Hurd Residence - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
  - Tompkins County Courthouse - Specifications, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
  - Tompkins Cooperative Fire Insurance Co. Building - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
  - Baptist Church - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
    Project # 249
  - Lorkin Residence - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
  - West Hill Grounds - Specifications - Holt, Architect, 1952 (Box 40)
    Project # 192 L
  - Corners Community Center Store Building, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1947 (Box 40)
    Project # 150
  - Corners Community Center Service Station, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 40)
  - Brand - Measurements, 1948 (Box 40)
  - Edmund Day Residence, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 40)
  - L.H. Durland - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 40)
  - Frozen Harvest, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1948 (Box 40)
  - Farren Residence, Skaneateles Lake, New York - Holt, Architect, 1948 (Box 40)
  - V.A. Fogg - Holt, Architect, 1947 (Box 40)
  - Haentjens Residence - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 40)
  - Ithaca Filter Plant - Holt, Architect, 1948 (Box 40)
  - John T. Lloyd Residence, Interlaken Beach, New York - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1949 (Box 40)
  - Clyde Moore Residence, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 40)
  - Dr. John A MacDonald Residence, Interlaken, New York - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 40)
    Project # 183
  - Dr. Leo H. Speno Residence - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1949 (Box 40)
  - H.B. Sutton Residence - Holt, Architect, 1949 (Box 40)
  - Theta Delta Chi Fraternity - Holt, Architect, 1947 (Box 40)
  - J.K. Uolita - Holt, Architect, 1949 (Box 40)
  - Wiegand, Herbert Pearsal Place (Box 40)
  - Dr. Hudson Wilson, 1949 (Box 40)
  - Dr. Ed F. Hall - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1951 (Box 40)
  - T.B. Maxfield (Box 40)
  - Seven Oaks, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1953 (Box 41)
  - J.C. Avery Residence, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1948 (Box 41)
  - J.E. Butterworth - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1948 (Box 41)
  - J.G. Pritchard & Son Inc., Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1951 (Box 41)
  - L.I. Grinnell, Ithaca, New York (Box 41)
  - Herbert W. Gledhill Jr., Watkins Glen, New York - Holt, Architect, 1953 (Box 41)
  - Gauntlett, John McGraw Gauntlett Residence - Holt, Architect, 1951 (Box 41)
    Project # 226
  - Community Chest Building, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1953 (Box 41)
  - Taylor Property/Scout Building, Lyons, New York - Holt, Architect, 1943 (Box 41)
  - Coop Store, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 41)
  - Administration Building - Finger Lakes State Park, Taughannock Falls State Park - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1960 (Box 41)
  - Administration Building Specifications - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1960 (Box 41)
  - Abott Residence - Holt and Downing, Architects, 1966 (Box 41)
    Project # 395
  - Alpha Chi Sigma, 1966 (Box 41)
  - Alpha Delta Phi, 1964 (Box 41)
    Project # 368
  - Clymes Residence - Presentation Material - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1966 (Box 41)
  - Cornell University Public Library, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 41)
  - Downsville Central School, Downsville, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1966 (Box 41)
  - Dryden Methodist Church, Dryden, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 41)
  - Glen National Bank, Watkins Glen, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1963 (Box 41)
    Project # 21033
  - Architect - The Ithaca Festival, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1966 (Box 41)
  - King Residence, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 41)
  - Roy H. Park, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1962 (Box 42)
  - Roy H. Park Broadcasting Inc., 408 East State Street, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Roy H. Park - Home Office, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Roy H. Park Apartments, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - R.H. Park Pool, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1963 (Box 42)
  - Roy H. Park, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects (Box 42)
  - Progressive Architecture Design Awards, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Squier Residence - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church, Owego, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Skaneatelles Lake - South Launching Site, 1965 (Box 42)
    Project # 405
  - Tioga Elementary School - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1964-1966 (Box 42)
  - C.E. Treman Beach House & Pool - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
    Project # 401
  - Waaland Residence - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1966 (Box 42)
    Project # 379
  - Watkins Glen Pool, Watkins Glen, New York, 1964 (Box 42)
  - Windsor Central School, Windsor, New York, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Urban Redevelopment Block, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Tompkins County Library, Ithaca, New York, 1963 (Box 42)
  - Tompkins County Trust Company - Demolition Specification, Ithaca, New York, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Mr. & Mrs. Paul Van Riper - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Chi Psi Frat - Certificate of Payment, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1964 (Box 42)
  - Ashford, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1964 (Box 42)
  - Audio Teaching Center - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Curtiss Residence - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Mr. Downing Correspondence, 1964 (Box 42)
  - Elmira Heights, New York - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1958 (Box 42)
  - Griffiss Air Force Base - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Holt, Sherwood (Box 42)
  - IBM Maintenance Contracts (Box 42)
  - Ithaca Hotel, 1964 (Box 42)
  - School Construction Systems Development - Movable Classrooms, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Jobs Turned Down, 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - County Library, 1965 (Box 42)
  - Nichols Golf Club House - Specifications (Box 42)
  - Tioga Recreation Center Nichols Golf Club (Box 42)
  - Palmer & Mills, Doctors Office Building, Horseheads, New York, 1966 (Box 42)
  - Phi Epsilon Phi Fraternity - Holt & Downing, Architects, 1965 (Box 42)
  - School Management (Box 42)
  - Sutton, H.B. - Holt, Architect, 1954 (Box 42)
  - Candor Central School, Candor, New York - Holt, Architect, 1953 (Box 42)
  - Owego Central School, Owego, New York - Holt, Architect, 1951 (Box 42)
  - 217 - Steel Takeoff & Struct Des, 1951 (Box 42)
  - Bd of Ed. West & East Clubhouses, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1949 (Box 42)
  - William Tucker Dean, 1954 (Box 42)
  - Delta Chi, 1949 (Box 42)
    Project # 188
  - Dryden Central School, Dryden, New York (Box 42)
  - G.L.F. Office Building, Ithaca, New York - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1948 (Box 42)
  - Douglas G. Gillette- Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 42)
  - Ithaca Gun Co., Ithaca, New York - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1953 (Box 42)
    Project # 194
  - Palmer, Henry O. Jr., Geneva, New York - Holt, Architect, 1952 (Box 42)
  - Rogalsky (Box 42)
  - Lewis W. Hooker, Hotnell, New York - Holt, Architect, 1954 (Box 42)
  - Kappa Delta Sorority, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1958 (Box 42)
  - Kennedy's Methodist Church (Box 42)
  - Trumansburg Central School, Trumansburg, New York - Holt, Architect, 1952 (Box 42)
  - Varna Community, Varna, New York - Holt, Architect, 1954 (Box 42)
  - Wallace, Syracuse, New York, 1952 (Box 42)
  - Wallace Steel and Supply Co.- Holt, Architect, 1953 (Box 42)
  - Struct. Design Post Office Garage, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1952 (Box 42)
    Project # 229
  - Dr. W.C. Geer Residence, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect, 1959 (Box 42)
    Project # 293
  - Hotel Taft - Expense Sheet, New York, New York, 1964 (Box 42)
  - U.S. Post Office Pre-Construction Design Data, Ithaca, New York (Box 43)
  - Tioga Central School, Tioga Center, New York - Holt, Architect, 1955 (Box 44)
  - Tioga School - Shop Drawings, Tioga Center, New York - Holt, Architect, 1953 (Box 44)
    Project # 224
  - Tioga Nichols School - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 44)
    Project # 264-268
  - Tioga Elementary School, Tioga Center, New York - Holt, 1957 (Box 44)
    Project # 264
  - Tioga Elementary School, Tioga Center, New York - Holt, Architect, 1957 (Box 45)
  - Nichola Elementary School - Holt, Architect, 1957 (Box 45)
    Project # 268
  - West Hill School - Shop Drawings - Holt, Architect, 1950 (Box 46)
    Project # 192
  - West Hill School - Specifications - Holt (Box 46)
  - Spencer Central School, Spencer, New York - Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 46)
  - Schuyler County Office Building - Shop Drawings/Specifications - Holt, Architect (Box 46)
    Project # 216
  - Ithaca Gun Co. Structural Design Data, Ithaca, New York - Holt, Architect (Box 46)
    Project # 218
  - Boynton Junior High School & Ithaca High School, Ithaca, New York - Specifications, 1954 (Box 46)
  - Ithaca High School - Structural Design, Ithaca, New York, 1964 (Box 46)
    Project # 358
  - Ithaca High School - Structural Design, Specifications, Addenda, Bids, Hardware Schedule, Color Schedule, Certificates of Payment, Job Correspondence, Supervisision Records, Punch Lists, Ithaca, New York (Box 47)
  - Ithaca High School - Concrete Test Reports, Soils Invenstigation Report, Architectural Shop Drawings, Ithaca, New York (Box 48)
  - Ithaca High School - Reinforcing Shop Drawings, Structural Steel Shop Drawings, Mechanical Shop Drawings, Electrical Shop Drawings, Ithaca, New York (Box 49)
  - Ithaca High School - Reinforcing Shop Drawings, Structural Steel Shop Drawings, Mechanical Shop Drawings, Electrical Shop Drawings, Ithaca, New York (Box 50)
  - Brockway Motors (Box 50)
    Project # 311
  - Macdonald Residence - Specifications - Holt & Gibb, Architects, 1949 (Box 51)
  - Acacia Fraternity - General, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Advertising Matter (Box 51)
  - Architect's Building (Box 51)
  - Bernard's (Box 51)
  - Brunner Scholarship (AIA), 1963 (Box 51)
  - Mr. Downing - Correspondence (Box 51)
  - Dr. W.C. Geer Residence, Ithaca, New York, 1964 (Box 51)
  - First National Bank - General, Ithaca, New York, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Doctor's Office Building, Horseheads, New York, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Education Committee - Central New York Chapter (Box 51)
  - 1964 Union Guide Educational Programs - Williamsport Building & Trades Council (Box 51)
  - Glen National Bank, Watkins Glen, New York, 1963 (Box 51)
  - Hill Residence, Ithaca, New York, 1963 (Box 52)
  - Holt and Downing, 1963 (Box 52)
  - Mr. Holt Correspondence (Box 52)
  - Mr. Holt's - Baths (Specs) (Box 52)
  - Hyde Bay Park Site, 1963 (Box 52)
  - Incoming Shop Drawings, 1962 (Box 52)
  - Contractor's Inquiries Ithaca Post Office (Box 52)
  - Marathon Bus Garage, Marathon, New York (Box 52)
  - Ordway, Donald E., 1962 (Box 52)
  - Pease Woodwork Company, 1962 (Box 52)
  - Ithaca Laundries - Petrillose Cleaners, Ithaca, New York, 1962 (Box 52)
  - Purchase Orders - Board of Education, 1961 (Box 52)
  - Purity Ice Cream, Ithaca, New York, 1962 (Box 52)
  - Speno Residence, 1963 (Box 52)
  - Change Notices - Tioga, Tioga Center, New York (Box 52)
  - Color Selection Drive-In Bank, Ithaca, New York (Box 52)
  - T.C.T.C. (Tompkins County Trust Company), Ithaca, New York, 1962 (Box 52)
  - Trefts Residence, 1963 (Box 52)
  - Watkins Salt Company, Watkins Glen, New York, 1963 (Box 52)
  - Watkins Glen Pool, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 52)
  - Ramada Inn, Ithaca, New York, 1972 (Box 52)
    Project # 72-457
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 52)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 53)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 54)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 54)
    Project # 446
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 54)
    Project # 447
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 54)
    Project # 448
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 55)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 55)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 55)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 56)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 56)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 56)
  - Photograph: Court Yard (Box 56)
  - Office Building Shepard Niles Crane & Hoist Corporation, 1970 (Box 56)
    Project # 409
  - Office Building Shepard Niles Crane & Hoist Corporation, 1970 (Box 57)
  - F.L.S.P.C. (Finger Lakes State Park Commission) Administration Building Addition, 1969 (Box 58)
    Project # 434
  - F.L.S.P.C. (Finger Lakes State Park Commission) Golf Facility, Sampson State Park, 1969 (Box 58)
    Project # 433
  - The "Hickories" Park, Owego, New York, 1969 (Box 58)
    Project # 69-440
  - Dryden Armory, Dryden, New York, 1985 (Box 59)
    Project # 588
  - Ithaca Savings and Loan Association, Ithaca, NY, 1966 (Box 60)
    Project # 394
  - Ithaca Savings and Loan Association, Ithaca, NY, 1966 (Box 61)
  - Savings Bank of Ithaca - Parking Lot, Ithaca, NY (Box 61)
  - Serling Residence (Box 61)
    Project # 431
  - Sampson State Park (Box 61)
  - Architectural Exhibitions, 1965 (Box 61)
  - TCTC (Tompkins County Trust Company) Parking Attd. Office (Box 61)
  - Fallout Shelters (Box 61)
  - New York State Association of Consulting Engineers (Box 61)
  - Chenango Valley State Park, 1969 (Box 61)
  - Monarch, Sydney, Ohio (Box 61)
    Project # 443
  - Monarch - Specifications (Box 61)
  - Office Building New York State Conservation Dept (Box 61)
  - Region 2 Headquarters, 1968 (Box 61)
    Project # 432
  - Region 2 Headquarters, 1968 (Box 62)
  - Roy H. Park Residence - Pool, 1962 (Box 62)
    Project # 350
  - Roy H. Park Residence - Specifications, 1962 (Box 62)
  - Cadillac Associates Inc. (Box 62)
  - Engineers, C.E. Acheson (Box 62)
  - Ithaca High School, Ithaca, New York, 1964-1966 (Box 62)
  - Ithaca High School - Specifications, Ithaca, New York (Box 62)
  - La Tourelle, Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 62)
  - Moog Inc. Plant 11B and Plant 11C (Box 63)
  - Moog Inc. Plant 11B and Plant 11C (Box 64)
  - Tennis Court, 1984 (Box 64)
  - Divi Divi (Box 64)
  - Cayman Brac Hotel Addition, 1984 (Box 64)
  - Cayman Brac (Box 64)
  - Tiara Beach (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 64)
  - Water - Desalinization & Purification (Box 64)
  - Fiberglass Tanks (Box 64)
  - Mary C. Robertson (Box 64)
  - Monarch, Cortland, New York (Box 64)
  - Wiggins Account (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 64)
  - Wiggins - West End Project (Box 64)
  - Divi Divi Corp., 1984 (Box 64)
  - Harborside Village, 1984 (Box 64)
  - Ramada Tower/Inn, Ithaca, New York (Box 64)
  - Dutch Village (Box 64)
  - Trumansburg Central School District, 1980 (Box 65)
    Project # 80-518
  - Trumansburg Central School District, 1981 (Box 65)
    Project # 81-532
  - Trumansburg Central School District, 1979 (Box 65)
    Project # 79-512
  - Schoolhouse Manor, 1983 (Box 65)
  - Ithaca Child Care Center - Fire code review, Ithaca, New York (Box 65)
  - Delavan Residence, 1984 (Box 66)
    Project # 84-582
  - Zwickel Residence, 1985 (Box 66)
    Project # 85-597
  - Krumhansl Residence, 1985 (Box 67)
    Project # 85-591
  - Nee Residence (Box 67)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co., Cortland, New York & Ohio (Box 67)
    Project # 403, 435
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co., Cortland, New York & Ohio (Box 68)
  - J.N. Adam Day Treatment Facility Job Files, 1986 (Box 68)
    Project # 86-609
  - J.N. Adam Day Treatment Facility Job Files, 1986 (Box 69)
  - J.N. Adam Day Treatment Facility Job Files, 1986 (Box 70)
  - Bailey Insurance, 1970 (Box 70)
    Project # 70-449
  - Corning Recreation Center, Corning, New York, 1968 (Box 70)
  - Baron Steuben Hotel Remodelling, Corning, New York, 1975 (Box 70)
    Project # 75-470
  - Owego Professional Building, Owego, New York, 1971 (Box 70)
    Project # 71-453
  - Springwood, 1970 (Box 70)
    Project # 70-461
  - OGS/DOT, Hamburg, New York, 1970 (Box 70)
    Project # 70-450
  - OGS/DOT, Hamburg, New York, 1970 (Box 71)
  - Finger Lakes State Park, 1966 (Box 71)
  - Taughannock Falls State Park - Comfort Station, 1966-1968 (Box 71)
    Project # 385
  - Reconstruction Home - Smoke Enclosure (Box 71)
  - Otisco (Box 71)
    Project # 417
  - Newark Valley Central School - Temporary School Building (Box 71)
    Project # 402
  - Long Point (Box 71)
    Project # 392
  - Lodi Point (Box 71)
    Project # 393
  - Lake Erie State Park (Box 72)
    Project # 370
  - Kerr, William B. (Box 72)
  - Fair Haven Beach Comfort Stations, 1967 (Box 72)
  - Elcor Nursing Home (Box 72)
    Project # 424
  - Erdmann (Box 72)
    Project # 384
  - William Tucker Dean Residence - Remodeling (Box 72)
    Project # 411
  - McGraw House (Box 72)
  - Gardner Road Elementary School (Box 72)
    Project # 374
  - General Services Administration, Post Office, Ithaca, New York (Box 72)
  - Chenango Valley State Park - Bathhouse - Concession (Box 72)
    Project # 351
  - Horseheads Elementary School, 1966 (Box 72)
  - Seneca Lake State Park, 1965 (Box 72)
    Project # 359
  - St. Paul's Church, Owego, New York (Box 72)
    Project # 381
  - Glen National Bank Addition, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 72)
    Project # 410
  - Glen National Bank Addition, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 72)
    Project # 408
  - Heggie's Remodeling (Box 72)
    Project # 387
  - Holcomb Residence (Box 72)
    Project # 396
  - Ewald Residence (Box 72)
    Project # 391
  - Owego Baptist Church, Owego, New York (Box 72)
    Project # 280
  - Danby Fire Station - Downing & Ass., Architects, 1968 (Box 72)
    Project # 68-426
  - Danby Fire Station- Downing & Ass., Architects, 1968 (Box 73)
  - Andes Swimming Pool, 1967 (Box 73)
    Project # 425
  - Brochure Materials (Box 73)
  - Gardner Road Elementary School, Horseheads, New York, 1965 (Box 73)
  - Gardner Road Elementary School, Horseheads, New York, 1965 (Box 74)
  - Gardner Road Elementary School, Horseheads, New York, 1965 (Box 75)
  - Skaneatelles Marina Park, 1969 (Box 75)
    Project # 69-441
  - Skaneateles Lake - North Launching Site (Box 75)
    Project # 404
  - Lodi Point, Seneca Lake, New York, 1967 (Box 75)
  - Long Point, Cayuga Lake, New York (Box 75)
  - Watkins Glen Swimming Pool, Watkins Glen, New York, 1966 (Box 76)
  - Fair Haven, 1963 (Box 76)
  - Taughannock Falls, New York, 1966 (Box 76)
  - Chenango Valley State Park, 1966 (Box 76)
  - Sampson State Park, 1967 (Box 76)
  - Seneca Lake State Park, 1965 (Box 76)
  - Whitney Point Boat Launching Site, 1967 (Box 76)
  - Lock 1, Cayuga and Seneca Canal (Box 76)
  - Otisco Lake, 1967 (Box 76)
  - Penn Yann Boat Launch (Box 76)
  - Watkins Glen, New York (Box 76)
  - TCTC (Tompkins County Trust Company) Seneca Building, Ithaca, New York (Box 76)
  - TCTC (Tompkins County Trust Company) Bookkeeping (Box 77)
  - Urban Renewal Submittal (Box 77)
  - Tuning Fork Building, 1969 (Box 77)
  - Region 2 Headquarters New York State Conservation Dept., 1968 (Box 77)
    Project # 68-432
  - Boat Launching Site, South Jamesport, Long Island, New York (Box 77)
  - "C" Specs D.O.T. (Box 77)
  - Delaware County Park, 1967 (Box 77)
    Project # 422
  - Lake Lauderdale State Park, 1968 (Box 77)
    Project # 427
  - Lake Lauderdale State Park, 1968 (Box 78)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 78)
  - Tioga High School, Tioga Center, New York, 1970 (Box 78)
    Project # 70-445
  - Tioga Elementary School, Tioga Center, New York (Box 78)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 79)
  - Tioga Elementary School, Tioga Center, New York (Box 79)
  - Tioga Elementary School, Tioga Center, New York (Box 80)
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. Edlund. - Design Data, Contracts, Specifications, Bid records, Finish & Hardware Schedules, Furniture, Soils Testing, Concrete Testing, Cortland, New York, 1966 (Box 80)
    Project # 66-403
  - Monarch Machine Tool Co. Edlund - Design Data, Contracts, Specifications, Bid records, Finish & Hardware Schedules, Furniture, Soils Testing, Concrete Testing, Cortland, New York, 1966 (Box 81)
  - Moog 4, 1978 (Box 82)
    Project # 78-498
  - Moog 4, 1978 (Box 83)
  - Moog Carleton, 1977 (Box 83)
    Project # 77-492
  - Moog Carleton, 1977 (Box 83)
    Project # 77-495
  - Moog, 1977 (Box 83)
  - Moog, 1977 (Box 84)
  - MOO58 Combined Support Maintenance Shop, Staten Island, New York, 1974 (Box 84)
    Project # 74-476
  - Ramada, Cortland, New York, 1974 (Box 85)
    Project # 73-463
  - Wrisley Schooley's The Pub, Ithaca, New York, 1974 (Box 85)
    Project # 74-465
  - L. Hope House, 1974 (Box 85)
    Project # 74-468
  - Dr. Gaffney Park Square, 1975 (Box 85)
    Project # 75-480
  - T.C.T.C. (Tompkins County Trust Company), Ithaca, New York, 1976 (Box 85)
    Project # 76-484
  - I.H.S. (Ithaca High School), Ithaca, New York, 1976 (Box 86)
    Project # 76-485
  - Flinn Residence, 1977 (Box 86)
    Project # 77-490
  - St. John's Episcopal Church, 1978 (Box 86)
    Project # 78-501
  - Old Courthouse (Tompkins County Courthouse), Ithaca, New York, 1979 (Box 86)
  - City of Ithaca Renewal Project, Ithaca, New York (Box 86)
    Project # 77-493
  - Moog - Five Year Facilities Plan 1977-1982, 1977 (Box 86)
  - Moog, 1978 (Box 86)
  - Moog, 1978 (Box 87)
  - Day Hospital, Watkins Glen, New York (Box 87)
  - I.H.S. (Ithaca High School), Ithaca, New York (Box 87)
  - Monkemeyer Skyrise Associates (Box 87)
  - Ithaca Country Club Proposed Additions (Box 87)
  - Tioga Schools, Tioga Center, New York (Box 87)
  - Strand Theater, Ithaca, New York, 1980 (Box 87)
    Project # 80-523
  - Brown, 1981 (Box 87)
    Project # 81-536
  - Ithaca Gun Company, Ithaca, New York (Box 88)
  - Trefts Residence (Box 88)
    Project # 348
  - Proposals: Cayuga Inlet, Albany Street, Seneca Building, Ithaca, New York (Box 88)
  - Specifications: Unknown Project (Box 88)
  - Brockway Boiler House (Box 88)
  - Ithaca Laundries - Petrillose Cleaners, Ithaca, New York (Box 88)
    Project # 335
  - J.N. Adam Job Files, 1986 (Box 89)
  - J.N. Adam Job Files, 1986 (Box 90)